Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein. This
is coffee toffee bar crunch. Let me show
you how to make it. For the base, we're
using fat-free Fairlife milk, vanilla
bean paste, instant coffee mix,
sweetener, salt, and zantham gum. All
you have to do is blend that up and then
throw it in your freezer for at least 16
hours. Hopefully you guys know the drill
by now. Take it out, run it under hot
water for about a minute, and then throw
it in your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. While that's spinning, we can
grab our mixins. We are using three mini
Heath bars. You can really use whatever
chocolate covered toffee you can find.
This is just what I had in the house.
Now, feel free to chop them up any way
you want. I found this little like
chopper thingy in my house. It's got to
be from like 1955, but shout out to my
parents for having it around. This was
the perfect and maybe only use case for
it. Now all that's left to do is top
your beautiful coffee ice cream with
that heath and you are good to go.